DANIJEL LAKIC

EDUCATION

Mid Sweden University - Computer Science

09/2019 to 06/2022

• Various courses in computer science 120hp

Malmö University

01/2020 to 12/2020

• Object-oriented programming with C# I and C# II

Luleå University of Technology

01/2020 to 12/2020

• Web Development with JavaScript, PHP and SQL databases

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

From the day I wrote my first line of code I knew I was hooked. My passion for programming lead me to master problem solving, ability to learn quickly and always to stay on the top of the new technologies. I am looking now for the right opportunity to develop my career. Developer with over 3 years of experience in developing as from university education as well as onside private projects.

WORK HISTORY

Freelance Web Developer 2021 - Current

- Doing some freelance developing on Fiver
- Mainly developing websites to private persons

Frontend Developer Trainee 05/2022 - 07/2022

Brainnest, Stockholm, SE

- The Brainnest Frontend Development Industry Training
- Development of websites and web applications using mainly JavaScript as well as Html and Css.

Supervisor, 11/2015 – Current, part time

SWEDEN MIGRATION AGENCY, Stockholm, SE

- Handled customer complaints, resolved issues, and adjusted policies to meet changing needs.
- Protected facility and property clients by regularly circulating premises and monitoring surveillance feeds.



•

0705889765



danijellakic@yahoo.com

PROFILES

- https://github.com/daniiellakic
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/danij el-lakic-9133b8143/

SKILLS

- Programming Languages: JavaScript, C#
- JS Framework: React
- Database SQL, MySQL
- Responsive Web Design
- Front-End Skills: HTML, CSS
- Version Control Systems: Git, GitHub
- Netlify
- Agile Workflow

 Contacted law enforcement in case of unauthorized persons, documents, and materials.

Care Assistant, 09/2013 - 10/2015

FANCY CARE AB, Stockholm, SE

- Ran errands for patients, did shopping, and picked up other necessities.
- Scheduled and accompanied clients to medical appointments.

LANGUAGES

Serbian:	Swedish:
Bilingual or Proficient (C2)	Bilingual or Proficient (C2)
English:	Spanish:
Bilingual or Proficient (C2)	Upper intermediate (B2)